# Nikolai Burnyshev

# Java Developer







79194485202



Ambitious Java Developer with >1 year of building software on Java and with 0.5 years experience in industrial development. Advanced in latest theologies and most effective ways of building software. Always focused on solving problems and open for gaining further experience.



#### Skills

Java Core

Spring Framework (with Spring Security)

SQL: Hibernate, PostgresSQL, Flyway

Git

Docker



# Work History

2022-10 - Current

## Junior Java Developer

ISavvy, Baku, Azerbaijan

- Build plugins for turning Minecraft into education platform.
- Developed Minecraft mechanics, such as rendering pictures and GIFs, audio playing and others.

#### 2022-08 - Current

### Java Developer Intern

КонсультантПлюс, Moscow, Russia

- Developed digital platform for providing juridical help for selfemployed.
- Developed telegram bot which helps people define their juridical status.
- Attended los of courses for product management, time management, programming methodologies, teambulding.
- Further developed in building RESTful web services.

#### 2022-04 - 2022-07

#### Java Developer Intern

ЛАНИТ Би Пи Эм, Moscow, Russia

- Developed internal web-application for automation the process of taking vacations.
- Learned how to work with Databases technologies, such as Hibernate, Flyway.
- Attended everyday meetings with senior developers for getting an advice and clarifying tasks. Passed code review after completing every task.
- Collaborated with testers, analytics, product managers for discussing developing process.
- Developed some frontend skills: HTML, CSS, JS, React, FetchAPI.



#### Education

2020-09 - Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science
Higher School of Economics - Moscow



Languages

English

